WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
♪ ("THE WHITE LOTUS"
THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (THEME MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
(WIND BLOWING)
LOCHLAN RATLIFF: This is what
it looks like before a tsunami.
(WAVES ROARING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
TIMOTHY RATLIFF: Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna tell you
everything. Hold on.
All right, Kenny Nguyen,
I met like 15 years ago.
Vietnamese guy,
worked at Markham Bradford,
in the division in Asia.
Anyway, I helped Kenny
set up this fund called Sho-Kel.
Look, this was not my idea.
You gotta understand that.
Please, find out whatever you can.
I'm just gonna be waiting for your call.
This is insane. Okay.
Thanks, Joe. Yeah.
♪ (INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com
♪ (WHIMSICAL MUSIC OVERLAPPING) ♪
Imagine this at home.
LAURIE: I mean, for sure,
but you have nothing but time.
- Good morning!
- LAURIE: Hi.
- Hi.
- Sawatdee kha.
Did you have a nice sleep?
- JACLYN: We did!
- Yeah.
Yeah, and thanks again
for such an amazing show
last night. It was...
We were just talking
about how fun it was.
- SRITALA: You like it?
- JACLYN: So fun.
- SRITALA: Oh, thank you.
- JACLYN: You're amazing.
- So nice to meet you.
- SRITALA: You are very kind.
- Enjoy!
- JACLYN: All right.
- SRITALA: Enjoy. I will see you.
- FABIAN: All right. Thanks.
Safe travels.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I had the most vivid dreams last night.
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- What were your dreams, Mom?
I could try to tell you what they mean.
I just remember I was on the beach,
and it was night. Uh...
And our house was there,
right by the water.
Then there was a tsunami.
Could be some kind of warning.
Yeah, so dreams predict the future now.
Okay, they might not predict the future,
- but they're a window into something.
- (CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
PIPER RATLIFF: I mean,
every symbol has a meaning.
It's the collective unconscious.
Yeah, and we all dream
about fire and snakes
because we're all afraid
of fire and snakes.
- I mean, it's not that deep.
- You know, you don't know everything.
Uh...
Just no more tsunami videos
before bed, okay?
LOCHLAN: Okay.
I've, uh, written a few songs, you know?
- SRITALA: Yeah, you told me.
- FABIAN: Yeah.
Maybe one night
I will sing for the guests.
- (DRINK POURING)
- FABIAN: That would be
a big step for me.
In my home, the artistic side
was not encouraged.
Uh...
That was an incredible show last night.
Oh, thank you so much.
No, really. You have so much presence.
I mean, élan, as they say.
Really. Uh...
- Could I sit for a second?
- SRITALA: Please, please, please.
Oh my God. Wow.
I am in the entertainment business.
- SRITALA: Oh! Yes?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I am a producer.
Here, working on a project actually.
- ♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Can't really go into it.
It's, um, kind of a high-profile thing.
But I know you used to be an actress.
I was.
Yeah. Well, I'm not sure
if you're still interested
in doing that,
but something tells me
that you might be.
This director that I'm working with...
Mm-hmm.
I would love for him to meet you.
Would you be open to that?
Do you take meetings?
He's a lot of fun. Really.
And I bet you are a lot of fun.
- (SRITALA CHUCKLES)
- (RICK HATCHETT LAUGHS)
I don't know. I think that you guys
would just really hit it off.
He's in Bangkok, though.
Oh! I'm leaving for Bangkok today.
- Are you...?
- Yes.
Serendipity.
- Could I get a... a contact?
- SRITALA: Sure.
- A number or something?
- Yeah. I'll give you my card.
That would be great.
SRITALA: Here.
Oh, well, I really, really wanna
make this happen, "Sri-tala."
- Sritala.
- "Srita-la."
- Sri...
- SRITALA: "Srita-la."
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh. Um, Sritala.
"Srita-la."
- Sritala.
- SRITALA: Yes.
Sritala.
- Sritala.
- Yes.
Mm.
- So sexy.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (SRITALA CHUCKLES)
Okay, I'll let you get back
to your meeting.
- Uh, I'll be in touch.
- All right.
I didn't get your name, but anyway...
- FABIAN: Fabian.
- RICK: Yeah.
(SIGHS)
What was that about?
Scorpio. So secretive.
It's not easy for me, Rick.
I'm an Aries.
I need everything out in the open.
My God, I need weed.
- Just tell me what's going on.
- (RICK SIGHS)
It doesn't concern you. Okay?
CHELSEA: Of course it concerns me.
Everything you do concerns me.
I'm your life partner, Rick.
(SCOFFS)
- AMRITA: Good morning.
- Hi!
I wanted to remind you
of our session this morning.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Mm-hmm.
I have a migraine.
I really look forward
to working with you again.
Yeah.
Thank you. Please help him.
Have a good breakfast.
I just wanna give you a heads-up.
Tomorrow, I'm going to Bangkok.
Why? What am I gonna do?
I don't know. Maybe you'll meet a guy
richer than me,
and you can sponge off him.
(SIGHS) I'm your soulmate, Rick.
- (SIGHS)
- ♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
How can you be my soulmate?
Our signs aren't even compatible.
- Good morning.
- KATE: Mm. Oh! Morning.
- Morning.
- LAURIE: Morning.
- Ready for some yoga?
- LAURIE: Mm. Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
And I was wondering, today,
maybe you'd like a session
with one of our energy healers?
What is an energy healer?
Well, we work to heal issues
in your body
using energy and your chakras.
- LAURIE: Mm.
- You said, um, "we."
Does that mean
that you're an energy healer?
It's something I do, yes.
JACLYN: Wow, very cool.
How long have you been working here?
Um, three years now.
Oh. Wait, so you came here
before the war?
I'm very lucky.
And... And where in Russia are you from?
Vladivostok.
Big port city, uh, far east of Russia.
I've never met anyone from Vladivostok.
VALENTIN: Actually, I have
a tattoo of it right here.
♪ (PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
And what did you do there?
- I worked in shipping.
- (LAUGHS)
- (KATE LAUGHS)
Did you come here with any family?
- No.
- No? Or girlfriend?
- VALENTIN: No.
- JACLYN: Okay.
So just yourself?
- Yes.
- JACLYN: All right.
Well, we are just so happy
that you are here and safe.
Thank you. Ladies,
I will see you in an hour.
- JACLYN: Mm-hmm.
- KATE: Okay.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
He just puts his hands over you
and heals you with his energy?
Laurie, you should have
a fling with him.
(LAUGHS) Why do you keep saying that?
It's the perfect week
for a fling. And you're single.
He probably wouldn't be into it anyway.
Are you kidding?
You are an attractive woman.
And he's a fling kinda guy. I can tell.
All you have to do is make a move.
Request him for an energy session.
- No.
- Oh, fine. I'll do it.
(CLEARS THROAT) Excuse me.
Can we please put in a request?
- PORNCHAI: Belinda.
- Ah! Sawatdee kha.
- (SIGHS)
- Sawatdee khrap. Good morning.
BELINDA LINDSEY:
Good morning. How are you?
Good. Good. I'm good.
Today's plan for you,
you are going to meet
some of the therapists
and they'll give you demonstrations.
- BELINDA: Mm.
- Then tonight,
I thought we could have dinner
and talk through everything.
- Sounds great.
- PORNCHAI: Good.
- Khop khun kha.
- Yin dee khrap. Pleasure.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- ♪ (INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(CELL PHONE CONTINUES VIBRATING)
Dad, seriously? Come on.
TIMOTHY: All right, all right.
(CELL PHONE CONTINUES VIBRATING)
PIPER: Dad, Jesus,
what is going on?
SAXON RATLIFF: Damn, Dad,
you're blowing up.
I got a lot going on.
Well, what's going on?
You want me to help you?
LOCHLAN: Yeah, is something wrong?
No, no.
Just, uh, work stuff.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(SLURPS)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
SARAH:
Tim, there are two men here
at the office from the FBI.
They're looking for you.
I gave them your number.
Just call me as soon as you can.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
CHUCK: It's Chuck.
I'm assuming you've heard.
The FBI's obtained a warrant,
and they're at your office.
I wish I had better news.
But I got called in, and I'm...
I'm gonna get all the information
on where everything stands.
I'm sure you're crawling
out of your skin right now,
but listen, do not talk to anyone
until you hear from me, okay?
Let me do my job,
and I'll get right back to you.
All right? Hang tight.
- Fuck me.
- (THAI PRAYER ECHOING)
(THAI PRAYER CONTINUES)
- (THAI PRAYER FADES)
- ♪ (SERENE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
GAITOK: Sawatdee khrap.
SRITALA: Sawatdee ja.
(IN THAI)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Uh...
Sawatdee khrap.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(IN ENGLISH) Holy shit! Dad. Look.
He didn't even run. He just stood there.
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
That happened here,
like, the next beach over.
Lochlan, do you wanna
keep giving us nightmares?
- Not really.
- Then put that down, please.
SAXON: Hey, Dad, uh,
Terry just messaged me.
He said that everyone in the office
is looking for you.
Should we, uh... Should we call in?
♪ (INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Uh, no, I... I'll deal with it.
No. Don't... Don't worry about it.
Well, what's going on? I mean...
- Sawatdee kha!
- Oh, yes, my blender, finally.
(CLAPS) Hey, Lochy, you want in on this?
On what?
Dude, a protein shake.
I said let's buffen you up.
How you doing, Pam?
PAM: Good, how are you?
How was it yesterday?
- Did you like your massage?
- Loved it.
Good, 'cause you've got
another one today with Pond.
I love Pond.
She's so gentle, but also firm.
PAM: The only other thing
that I have scheduled today
is for Lochlan. Our corrective
posture treatment.
- Corrective posture?
- Honey, you should go.
SAXON: Yeah, so just put,like,
two scoops of this.
- PAM: Two scoops of that.
- SAXON: This, the creatine,
some peanut butter. What kind
of milks do you guys have?
PAM: Um, goat, oat, cow, soy.
Dad, did... did my phone just ring?
- No.
- Sounded like it rang.
- And just put both of these in there.
- I can do that.
- Okay. Thank you, Pam.
- Don't worry about it at all. At all.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh, God, it's just nonstop
with these phones, y'all.
Wait, who is it, Dad?
I mean, is it Terry?
Wait, why'd you...
why'd you just do that?
- What are you doing?
- No. Gimme that. Hey. I, uh...
No. You know, I've been thinking.
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- And... and, uh,
I changed my mind.
You know, Piper's right.
It's nonstop with the phones.
So, uh, let's do it.
Let's do it. Let...
Let's give our phones to Pam.
- What?
- Really?
Yeah.
(SCOFFS) What... what...
What, are you kidding me?
It's a rare thing
that we're together like this.
So, let's make the most of it.
Let's make...
make this week special, right?
- Yeah?
- No.
Yeah! Just give your stuff to Pam.
No! Pam, my ass. I'm... No!
Hey, watch your mouth now.
Pam, you... you got your...
the, uh, bag thing? Do you have it?
I sure do, and I'll even
bring out the big one
so you can just put it all in there.
I think it's a great idea, honey.
You're gonna be so much more relaxed.
Yeah.
So, uh...
Well, come on, guys.
What are you waiting for? Come on!
- Get your phones.
- SAXON: (SCOFFS) Wait, what?
Dad, you're just gonna give her my phone
- because Piper's having...
- Yeah.
Some sort of Buddhist identity crisis?
You can live for five days
without your precious phone.
No, we traveled 35 hours
to Thailand for you, okay?
- You always get what you want.
- Hey, hey, hey!
You get everything you want
all the time.
- No, Piper, you always get what you want!
- Hey! Saxon.
- Saxon! Piper.
- What are you talking about?
SAXON: Dad, she
always gets everything. It...
Son, son! Come on. Come here.
Just take it. I don't even care.
I know I don't have a ton
going on at work right now,
but I still need  to be available,
you know?
I mean, I'm trying to build
my own client list here, Dad.
I understand, but... but, son, bud,
I... You know, I'm...
(SIGHS)
I'm so impressed by you.
You... You're gonna have
a phenomenal career.
I can see it.
- (EXHALES) Really, you think?
- No, I... I know it.
(CHUCKLES) I mean,
I know I tell you this
all the time, Dad, but...
I love working.
- You know?
- Yeah.
SAXON: And I love working with you.
I mean, I get to learn so much from you.
Look, we both know
how gratifying work is.
But, I mean...
there's gotta be more to life,
right, than just success.
(HESITATES) And if we...
we leave room for them to develop,
then... then we'll end up
having more to offer.
You know what I'm saying?
You understand?
- Yeah.
- TIMOTHY: Yeah.
So let's d... do this.
Let's try it. Let's...
- It'll be a great experiment.
- ♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Uh, sure. Okay.
- TIMOTHY: Okay.
Can I just call Terry and tell him
I'm not gonna be reachable?
No.
- No?
- No, let's just...
- Let's walk away clean.
- SAXON: Dad, I...
No. We'll come back
in a week, refreshed,
and then we'll take over the world.
Huh? You and me, pal. What do you say?
Uh, okay. Yeah.
- Right.
- What are you doing?
I'm taking your watch.
- Are you serious, Dad? My watch?
- Yeah.
If we're gonna do this thing,
we're gonna do it 100 percent.
Now, you go get your computer.
PAM: Good. Okay.
- All right.
- PAM: Okay.
And have I got your phone, Mr. Ratliff?
- Huh?
- ♪ (TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
Yes, your phone?
Oh, uh, my phone? Uh...
Well...
Yeah. All right.
Oh, you're gonna be so glad
that you did this.
This better go in your safe.
A lot of important stuff on there.
- (CHUCKLES) What, your porn?
- Shut up!
- Thank you so much.
- And yes.
You've all done really well.
This isn't even that much,
I don't think. Okay, um...
Bye-bye.
(SCOFFS)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
♪ (UPBEAT POP SONG PLAYING) ♪
Khop khun kha.
- Hey!
- Sawatdee kha.
Sawatdee kha.
- Shall we?
- Yes, let's.
So, um, do y'all wash people's feet too?
- Yes.
- (CHUCKLES)
Okay, so that's a real thing.
♪ (VOCALIST SINGING IN THAI) ♪
Sritala.
♪ (SONG CONCLUDES) ♪
I mean, what the fuck
are we even supposed to do now?
Mm.
No, like... like, finish it.
Like, gulp it.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Yes. There we go. (LAUGHS)
(BURPS)
(GAGS)
Don't you want the big dogs
to respect you?
What, you wanna be neurotic
your whole life
and die a fucking virgin?
- No.
- No!
So let's get you laid,
like, this week. I'll help.
Okay? All hands on deck.
- LOCHLAN: Yeah.
- (CHUCKLES)
♪ (INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Hey, what's up?
All right, I gotta go.
Gotta get
to my posture correction class.
- All right. Hey, Lochy.
- LOCHLAN: Yeah?
(CHUCKLES)
VALENTIN: Breathe out
into downward-facing dog.
♪ (INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
VALENTIN: Neck is forward.
There you go.
(WHISPERS) Laurie.
(SNORTS)
- (MOUTHS) Fuck you.
VALENTIN: And then slowly
step your right foot forward,
or lightly jump.
(ALL SPEAKING THAI)
GAITOK: Mook?
- (IN THAI)
- (IN ENGLISH) Okay. Bye.
MOOK: (IN THAI)
(CHUCKLES)
(IN ENGLISH) God...
(IN THAI)
(IN ENGLISH) Thank you.
(CHUCKLES)
Mm.
(GAITOK CHUCKLES)
GAITOK: Ja.
- (IN ENGLISH) Okay?
- (IN THAI)
(IN ENGLISH) Okay. Ja.
(BIRD CALLING)
- (INSECTS CHIRPING)
- (MONKEY CALLING)
AMRITA: In your stillness,
be aware of your sensations.
- (EXHALES)
- AMRITA: What do you feel?
I don't know.
Look, you seem like a really nice lady,
but this is... this is not my thing.
AMRITA: Underneath anger,
there's always a sadness.
Something we are grieving.
What are you grieving?
I've done a lot of bad things.
Trust me.
I made a lot of mistakes.
(SIGHS) Whatever.
And yeah, yeah, my...
And my father, he was a good man.
He was a decent man.
But... I never got
to know him, you know,
because he was murdered.
And...
And I can't get my life back.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
But maybe I can still get
some satisfaction.
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
- (INSECTS CHIRPING)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Hi! Uh, sawatdee kha.
My name is Piper Ratliff.
I've been emailing with Burin?
Oh. Burin is not here.
Oh, um... I... I just...
I'm... I'm visiting
from America this week,
and he said
he was gonna set up a meeting
with me and Luang Por Teera?
Because I'm considering
the year program.
I'm... I'm finishing college,
and then I would start this summer.
Luang Por cannot meet today.
Maybe Friday at 2:00?
Two o'clock. Okay, uh,
thank you so much.
Uh. Khop khun kha.
- Okay. See you Friday.
- See you Friday. Bye.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Better if you keep your eyes closed.
- Oh, sorry.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
♪ (MUSIC BUILDS, SOFTENS) ♪
You sit in a defensive posture.
- You pleaser? People pleaser?
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
A lot of big personalities in my family.
You meet people
on their plane of reality.
But what is your reality?
I thought this was about
helping me with my posture?
'Cause now you have
your left foot on right knee.
You're protecting yourself
with your female side.
How long is this session?
(BIRD CALLING)
Gary barely ever talks to me.
He's so secretive.
He has an ex-wife,
but he never talks about her.
CHELSEA: Mm?
All I know is that
she was a real mental patient.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- How bad?
- Like, "killed herself" bad.
Oh my God!
Yeah. One day, she was so depressed,
she couldn't take it anymore.
She just walked out into the ocean
and kept going, and never came back.
- What?
- All they found was, like...
like, a part of her leg.
Fucking hell!
- Hey.
- CHELSEA: Oh, hey, babe.
- I need to get weed.
- You all right?
I'm going to town.
- Sorry. I better go.
- Yeah, you should.
- Love ya.
Hey!
- Hey!
- You mind if I sit here?
I'm not getting
good sunlight over there.
Sure.
(SAXON GRUNTS)
Hey, I'm Saxon, by the way.
I'm Chloe.
- Nice to meet you.
- CHLOE: Nice to meet you.
(SAXON CHUCKLES)
I hear you're a douche.
(LAUGHS)
♪ ("A THAI WEDDING"
BY IMADE SAPUTRA PLAYING) ♪
(CHUCKLES)
♪ (SINGER VOCALIZING) ♪
♪ (VOCALISTS SINGING IN THAI) ♪
Jesus Christ! What is your deal?
- Gotta be fucking kidding me.
- (ENGINE REVS)
(IN THAI)
(CHUCKLES)
BODYGUARD:
Gaitok.
(SPEAKING THAI)
(IN THAI)
♪ (SONG CONTINUES) ♪
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
♪ (SONG CONCLUDES) ♪
(IN ENGLISH) Hey, should I buy this?
Uh, yeah, sure.
- Feeling better?
- Mm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Are we ever gonna have fun again?
Yeah, sure.
You wanna get fucked up?
- It's 2:00 in the afternoon.
- So what?
We have dinner tonight
with Chloe and Gary.
Wh... Why?
'Cause the hotel are having
a barbecue on the beach.
- It'll be really nice.
- (GROANS) I just...
Snake show.
- What?
- RICK: Mm. A snake show.
Come on!
VICTORIA RATLIFF: I'm proud
of you for giving up your phone.
TIMOTHY: Mm-hmm.
I know that was hard.
TIMOTHY: Thanks, babe.
You seem tired.
Why don't you take a nap?
I don't do naps. You know that.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(TIMOTHY SIGHS)
Why don't you take one of these?
Not my thing, okay? It's your thing.
(SIGHS) They're not addictive.
I just take 'em when I need it.
TIMOTHY: No, but I like to...
Nah, I don't wanna be foggy.
You make fun of me, but they work.
(SIGHS)
- It's not a big deal.
- Thanks.
Oh, I gotta get ready for my massage.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(SIGHS)
It's fucked up they're stuck
inside these cages.
Yeah? Where should they be, Rick?
Out in the fields, with the farmers?
They're venomous snakes.
They still got a right to live free.
Not if they're out biting people.
SHOW HANDLER: Hello, everybody!
You can follow me,
and the show start now.
Khop khun kha.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪ (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(COBRA HISSING)
EMCEE: Okay,
the first show for you, everybody.
This is the cobra,
the Thailand cobra, Naja cobra.
(COBRA HISSES)
EMCEE: It is the poison snake
and the venomous snake,
dangerous snake.
Have a lot everywhere, in Thailand,
in the city, in the forest,
in Southeast Asia,
Thailand, Malaysia, Indonesia,
India, a lot of cobra.
- (COBRA HISSES)
- (CROWD GASPS)
Don't try that at home.
Wow.
The poison
can kill person in one bite...
cobra bite, 30 minutes...
- (DISTORTION STOPS)
- (CLICKS TONGUE) ...gone. Die.
- (COBRA HISSES)
- EMCEE: But don't worry.
Fifteen minutes, go hospital.
- It's not far from here.
- (COBRA HISSES)
EMCEE: Many snake,
we get him from the house.
He come up on the toilet,
in the bathroom.
- A lot the cobra.
- (COBRA HISSES)
(HISSING CONTINUES)
♪ (EERIE MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
(CHIPS CRUNCHING)
(COBRAS HISSING)
- EMCEE: The next show is python.
- (BOX LID CLATTERS)
EMCEE: The python
is the world's longest snake.
- (DISTORTION STOPS)
- ♪ (MUSIC ENDS ABRUPTLY) ♪
EMCEE: The python can kill
the big animal. Yes.
EMCEE: (IN DISTANCE)
An animal like a cow.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(EMCEE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
♪ (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
♪ (LIVELY FOLK SONG PLAYING) ♪
(SNAKE HISSES)
It's okay. It's okay. You're free.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Go, go, go!
Whoa! Yeah. That's right.
(WHISPERS) That's right, buddy.
Go, go, go, go. Find a tree.
Find a really good tree.
(BREATHES HEAVILY) Get out.
Go, go, go, go.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
EMCEE: Now, put the python
around your neck
and take a picture. Smile.
Wow. Say "cheese."
Rick?
What are you doing?
- ♪ (SONG CONCLUDES) ♪
- (COBRA HISSES)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GASPS)
(CHELSEA SCREAMING)
- (SPEAKS THAI)
- (YELLING IN THAI)
RICK: Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey! Hey!
- Where are they taking her?
- EMPLOYEE: Hospital, hospital.
- The hospital?
- So she don't die.
- Rick!
- Die? Die? Hey! Hey! Hey, wait!
- Hey! Hey!
- (TIRES SCREECH)
Fuck!
(HORN HONKING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
- The hospital!
- Okay, okay.
- Go, go.
- (ENGINE REVS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪ (ENCHANTING MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MELLOW FOLK ROCK SONG PLAYING) ♪
♪ (VOCALIST SINGING IN THAI) ♪
God, Chelsea!
I know.
I can't believe you got bit by a cobra.
Why would you release a cobra?
I... I think, uh,
the weed that I was smoking was laced.
I mean, Chelsea, you've had
two brushes with death
- in two days.
- Yeah.
Like, maybe you guys shouldn't
come on the boat tomorrow.
- (CHUCKLES)
- What boat?
Gary has a boat.
And he's invited some people,
and they want us to come.
CHLOE: It's gonna be
a fun group, a lot of expats.
- Oh, great.
- We're gonna tour around the island.
It's gonna be fun.
Yeah, yeah, it sounds like a...
a really good time.
(LAUGHS)
- KATE: Oh.
- Mm!
How was your healing session
today, Laurie, with Valentin?
Mm, it was interesting.
Mm. Did he get his energy inside you?
- (LAUGHS)
It was kind of intimate.
I haven't been
not touched by a man
like that in a long time.
- Mm!
- With stuff like that...
I don't know, it's either
goofy or spooky. I just...
I'm just not a New Age kind of person.
It all feels kind of...
- witchy, to me.
- That's what I like about it.
Yeah, 'cause like Christianity,
and most religions,
they're made for men, right?
The father sacrifices the son,
the son's a man, dies on the cross,
the heroes are all men,
and the women just cry on the sidelines.
Mm. You want the woman
to be centered in the story?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's all just so male.
You know, the epic battle
for good and evil
just doesn't speak to me.
Well, I'm a woman, and...
I get a lot out of going to church.
Hm.
I just... I love the people.
It's very moving.
I didn't know you went to church.
- Oh, yeah! We go every Sunday.
- Mm.
Yeah, ever since we moved to Austin.
But is it like a real Texan church?
Like with Bible thumpers and...
Well, the people are, you know,
more conservative than, like,
L.A. people or...
- like New York.
- Mm-hm.
Is that weird for you?
Why would it be weird?
I... I don't know.
If I was just around a bunch of Texans
who voted for Trump,
I guess I'd just feel a little,
you know, alienated.
They're nice people.
Really good families.
Cool.
But do you ever talk politics with them?
Sometimes.
And it doesn't get awkward?
- Why would it?
- Because!
Wait. Are... are you a Republican?
- No!
- Oh. Okay.
I'm an independent. But Dave is.
An independent?
- Mm-hmm.
- JACLYN: Since when?
You didn't vote
for Trump, though, did you?
- (CHUCKLES)
- (JACLYN CHUCKLES)
Are we really gonna talk
about Trump tonight?
Listen, it is a very pretty church.
It is not weird at all.
And I will take you
if you ever come visit me in Austin.
- I can't wait to get down there.
- I really wanna come.
- Mm-hmm.
- KATE: Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- What a great day.
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
And I love those ladies.
Everyone loves you too.
It's only been two days,
and I already feel rejuvenated.
Everybody's so genuine,
and nobody's jaded.
You know, that shit's refreshing.
So, you like Thailand?
- Very much.
- I am happy.
Mm.
You know, before I got here, I was...
depressed.
♪ (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
My friend...
He was my boss, actually. He...
died in this freak accident at work.
And this woman, this rich woman,
she was supposed
to help me open up my own spa,
you know, so I could be my own boss.
Something I've always wanted to do.
And of course, she flakes.
Runs off with some guy she just met.
Ah!
(SCOFFS)
What? What is it?
I saw someone yesterday,
and I knew I recognized him.
But I think he's...
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
How big is the boat?
- How big is the boat? It's huge.
- CHELSEA: Mm.
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
- Hi.
Good evening, everybody. (CHUCKLES)
Um, really sorry to interrupt, but...
- do I know you?
- ♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Uh...
- I work at the White Lotus in Maui,
and I'm pretty sure I met you there.
GARY: Um...
I don't think so.
Greg, isn't it?
- It's Gary.
- Huh? Really?
Did you date a woman
named Tanya McQuoid?
Me? (SCOFFS) No.
BELINDA: (CHUCKLES) Okay.
Well, he must have
a doppelganger then... (LAUGHS)
because I swear
you look just like this man
I met in Maui.
(SCOFFS) Anyway.
Sorry to bother you, guys.
Enjoy your night.
- CHLOE: Yeah, no problem.
- CHELSEA: Thank you!
CHLOE: Thank you.
I told you, Gary,
all you bald White guys look alike.
Hmm.
(SCOFFS)
Lochy, sweetie,
did they correct your posture?
There wasn't enough time.
Hey, tomorrow's the full moon, you guys.
And it's supposed to be
like a really big holiday here.
And I got us invited on a guy's yacht
so we can go cruise around the islands.
Who did you meet with a boat?
Are they decent people?
Yeah, they own their own yacht.
They're rich.
Just because people are rich
doesn't mean they're not trashy.
Most rich people are trashy.
I wouldn't go that far.
No. And where's Dad? Is Dad okay?
(SNORES, BREATHES DEEPLY)
VICTORIA:
The jet lag's been hard for him.
He hasn't been sleeping well,
and he finally just conked out.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SOFTLY) Fuck.
(SIGHS)
♪ (BROODING RENDITION OF
"THE WHITE LOTUS" THEME MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SECURITY GUARD SPEAKING THAI)
(GAITOK SPEAKING THAI)
(SPEAKING THAI)
(BOTH SPEAKING THAI)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
(IN THAI)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
RICK: (IN ENGLISH) Frank, hey,
it's your old buddy Rick.
Hey, I'm coming to Bangkok tomorrow.
Really love to see ya.
I need your help
with a couple of things.
Give me a call when you get this, okay?
All right. Later, man.
Rick...
you released a bunch
of venomous snakes today.
You do realize that?
- (RICK SIGHS)
- (CHUCKLES)
- You're fucking deranged!
- I felt bad for 'em.
Snakes are evil. Read the Bible.
Well, even evil things
shouldn't be treated like shit.
It's only gonna make them more evil.
Yeah! Well, I could have been killed.
(SIGHS) I was stoned.
- (SIGHS)
- ♪ (SOFT MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
RICK: I'm sorry.
You're not gonna
get rid of me that easy.
If you kill me, I'll follow you
into the next life,
and the next.
You'll never get rid of me.
(BOTH SMOOCH)
You're insane.
Insane.
(RICK SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
BELINDA: You didn't have
to walk me all the way back.
- Aw, I have to. Come on.
- I appreciate you. (LAUGHS)
- PORNCHAI: Okay.
- Thank you.
(CHUCKLES) You're welcome.
BELINDA: No, really.
Thank you for dinner and today.
I had a great time.
I'm sorry, I don't usually drink.
- Come on! It was fun. (LAUGHS)
- (PORNCHAI LAUGHS)
Um...
I hope you have good dreams of me,
and I will have good dreams of you.
Is that a Thai expression?
Uh...
- Good night.
- Oh. Good night.
- (LAUGHS)
- (PORNCHAI LAUGHS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
Tipsy, tipsy.
Hmm.
What you dreaming about, Pornchai?
(FAINT CREAKING)
♪ (SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Fuck is that?
- (INSECTS CHIRPING)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(JACLYN AND LAURIE LAUGHING IN DISTANCE)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
(JACLYN AND LAURIE
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LAURIE LAUGHING)
(JACLYN AND LAURIE
CONTINUE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(JACYLN LAUGHING)
(LAURIE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
- JACLYN: Yeah, she...
- LAURIE: You know what?
She's always been like this.
Always taking on the attitude
of the person she's with.
- JACLYN: Dave!
- LAURIE: I know.
- The look on your face was killing me.
- JACYLN: Oh, God.
LAURIE: I was trying to kick you
under the table.
Are you kidding?
I didn't even know what to say.
I mean, Trump? (CHUCKLES)
I mean, are you insane?
LAURIE: Well, she's always
let Dave call the shots, though.
JACLYN: I can't even imagine
what it's like living in Texas.
She's probably just doing it to fit in.
As a woman, it's just
so self-defeating, right?
I'm still kind of in shock.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Look, I know people
get more conservative
- the older that they get, but...
- LAURIE: Oh, sorry.
(PILLS RATTLE)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(GROANS)
You think you'll be able to sleep
- after you napped all day?
- ♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
(SIGHS) Uh-huh.
You want one of my pills?
I don't take drugs.
- They really work.
- (BREATHES DEEPLY)
Tim, is something going on?
- ♪ (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (INSECTS CHIRPING)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
sync and corrections by solfieri
www.MY-SUBS.com
♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪